First, we're going to do an exercise of multiple-choice questions with
single answer in part three.
In step one, we have to read the questions to predict the
structure of the recording.
From these five questions, we can see that there are two students,
Ben and Anna, in the conversation.
In question one, we know that for some reason Ben missed the
professor's lecture, and Anna attended that lecture, so Anna told Ben about it.
The topic is about astronomy and stargazing workshops because these two
keywords are frequently mentioned in the questions and options.
In step two, you have to underline the keywords in the questions and options.
Remember to underline nouns, main verbs, adjectives and adverbs, and ignore all
the grammatical words.
Now let's do a small practice.
Great job!
In step three, for questions one to four, move your mouse cursor
to the keywords being mentioned while listening, and cross out the incorrect information.
For question five, you should draw a table with two columns to
identify which viewpoint two students agree on.
Next you're going to listen to the recording and find the correct
answers to these five questions.
Step four, choose the correct answer.